(Amy:)Sheldon, you being here might
not be making things better.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Sheldon:)And is that why
everybody was invited but me?
(Amy:)They didn't invite
everybody but you.
(Amy:)Bernadette invited me,
(Amy:)and Stuart lives here.
(singsongy):
Who wants hot cinnamon rolls?
(Official:)So, when you hear the music,
that's your cue.
(Official:)Any questions?
(Leonard:)Oh, the package
that we paid for
(Leonard:)said the aisle was supposed
to be strewn with rose petals.
(Official:)Where are the rose petals?!
WOMAN: We're out!
You know what?
(Leonard:)It's fine.
WOMAN: We can use the
potpourri from the bathroom!
(Penny:)Really, we're good.
(chuckles)
(Leonard:)Yup, just want
to get married.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
Great.
(Official:)I'll see you two
up there.
(Leonard:)This is it.
I know.
(Leonard:)I love you.
(Penny:)I love you, too.
WOMAN: Was that a yes
or no on the potpourri?!